fatbit.com 2019-11-17

# What information do we collect?

                             FATbit Technologies – Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our
site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address,
phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
        To personalize your experience: Your information helps us to better respond to your
         individual needs
        To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based
         on the information and feedback we receive from you
        To improve customer service: Your information helps us to more effectively respond to
         your customer service requests and support needs
        To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold,
         exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever,
         without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased
         product or service requested.
        To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
        To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing, may be
         used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to
         receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information,
         etc.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal
information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer hard
drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers
systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use
cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data
about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in
the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better
understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the
information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

A cookie might contain any of the following:
- The amount of time you spend on a website
- The links you click while using the website
- The options, preferences or settings you choose
- Recording which pages you've visited in the past
- Items in a shopping basket
If you do not wish to use this feature
You can switch off cookies in your browser settings.
You may add Google analytics’ browser plug-in here
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable
information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website,
conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is
appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights,
property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our
website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore
have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.
Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about
these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance
with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal
information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection
Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 14 years of age. Our website,
products and services are all directed to people who are at least 14 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to
information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and
limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.fatbit.com
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Right to access
Under GDPR guidelines, right to access allows you to ask for your personal data in verbal or
written form. Please request the same at info@fatbit.com.
Right to be forgotten
Under GDPR guidelines, right to be forgotten allows you have the right to ask us to remove your
information. Please request the same at info@fatbit.com.
Data Portability
Under GDPR guidelines, the right to data portability allows individuals to obtain and reuse their
personal data for their own purposes across different services. Please request the same at
info@fatbit.com.
You can read more about GDPR here.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the
information below.
https://www.fatbit.com
Head Office
FATbit Technologies
(Ably Soft Pvt Ltd)
Plot 268, Sector-82,
JLPL Industrial Area,
Mohali, Punjab, India

Branch Office
FATbit Technologies
(Ably Soft Pvt Ltd)
Unit No. A-712, Tower A,
7th Floor, Bestech Business Towers,
Sector 66, Mohali, Punjab
